Why have the invocation but a five-pass or first-class church which really always?
Father, thank you for the privilege of living here in the city.
And I thank you for the audience and ask that you bless them tonight as they share,
but also especially our men and women up front.
Father, in those moments when something doesn't go right, give them special peace,
give them extra joy when the things they've worked on come together.
Most of all, Lord, I thank you for the him and want you to bless them and bless our men.
You should be meeting tonight. Jesus name, I pray. Amen.
I'd like to thank you.
Please, to the flag of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which the Sands Foundation, under God, and the Biblical,
we're living here in justice tomorrow.
Four public and good, let's give them personal appearances.
Five, cutting list.
Most of them.
Second.
Estep.
High.
Jones.
Third.
Five.
Six clients are in your concrete.
Most of them.
Second.
Estep.
High.
Jones.
Third.
Seven minutes from the July 1st, 2020.
Four regular meetings.
Most of them.
Second.
Third.
Jones.
High.
Eight.
The March 18 2024.
Minutes.
History of the Group.
Shutting.
Six hour.
Doful.
That's one of those.
Darker.
их.
None.
Valid.
First.
Old Colleane in legislation.
Tell me your honor.
Is it 2688?"
yok 3.
low bills.
Last year sermon you call it COVAKE.
stream for right-winger.
Part of the Part of C件.
Part of reported bondages.
So the city of Miami folks don't review proceedings,
findings, and other documentation.
So it's just things, it's DM safety issues.
They're less than the anxiety plan.
It's disseminated, it's sediment transport study.
There's been some communications with the lead agency.
And also some meetings that we've had internally
with our legal team.
So at the 750,000 budget of GDRDA claims,
the current balance is 263,310 dollars and 14 cents.
If this current invoice is approved,
you'll even remain balanced up 245,680 dollars.
Most to approve.
I don't want to.
Joe, it's high.
Perfect.
Okay.
Tann, you know,
Stratton Edmund, the Palmer Klein for
Georgia, it relies on the amount of $795.
Yes.
This is for professional services and
this person that incurred from May 21st to June 20th.
And this is for a good
Stratton Edmund and Palmer.
This is communications with our legal team.
I'm also reviewing some first documents,
different things like that.
Of the $750,000,
but just for the GRD claims,
the current balance is $2.45,
681.98.
If this is of $795,
is approved,
we'll have a remaining balance of $244,886.
And 98 cents for fiscal year,
2324.
Motion to approve.
Second.
So.
Is that.
Joe,
Hi.
All right.
11.
The other new business of inobits have been posted since the
post of the agenda.
12 staff reports.
13 trusted community announcements.
14.
This meeting will be continued from council chambers,
reconvening the staffer and the purpose of
executive session.
That's a completion of the regular meeting of the
month city council.